This is Cheeteru Bishaku.
I, Hanaho Kobayashi, will be your host today.
Happy New Year, everyone!
Yay!
It's been about 10 months since I've been here?
No, it's been a year. It's been almost a year.
What have you been doing?
I haven't been here since last October.
Happy New Year!
I'm closer to "let's make a good sound" now.
Yes, it is. I really do.
Thank you very much.
Please take care of me.
Yes, I'm Ayaka Yasumoto, attendance number 5.
Please take care of her.
I'm Ayaka Yasumoto, attendance number 5. Pleased to meet you.
Yay!
Yes, that's why I have two friends here today.
They are here today!
It's a winning participation, isn't it?
I thought.
When the SHOWROOM members came,
Oh, they are my friends, they are my friends.
First of all, and second of all.
I felt like I was in a café today.
I feel like I'm in a cafe today, and I'm here to deliver this message.
Well, I'd like to start right away.
The Shrimp in the Shrimp
The Hilarious and Fufufu Showroom of Ebichu
Thank you for watching the 49th edition of Ebichu's Delightful and Frivolous Showroom.
I'm going to show you the showroom of the shrimpers.
I've said it many times!
This program is about our little sister, Uka-chan, the showroom's little sister.
Uka-chan's showroom is our little sister showroom. I'd like to announce the ranking of the showrooms.
First of all, I'd like to announce the 5th place, Mr. Eyebrow. Thank you very much.
It's not me.
You are making it thinner today. It's not me. Fourth place.
First place, Ms. Yui, Maya Aya Kaoriko.
Good!
Everyone's in! Everyone's in!
That's great!
Thank you!
So this is Maya Aya.
Third place, Po-chan, Ega.
Thank you!
Second place, Mr. Takeshi.
1st place, Ms. Penrabunbun
Thank you!
Yes, so you are the original avatar of the Binaka showroom.
We appreciate you registering with our showroom,
You can get it for free or for a fee if you press the "Gifting?
You can get it if you press the button. Please do so. It's amazing, isn't it? It has a strong presence, doesn't it?
It matches the red check. It matches with today's background. It's a collaboration with Sanrio.
There was a girl who was distributing the showroom, and when I peeked in, yes, she was there!
I peeked in, and there was this, I can't take a picture right now, but this icon, that's the one...
I saw someone using the Ebimonzine. I'm visiting the other distribution.
I thought, wow, it's one of ours that really has a presence.
I hope you all will be able to get it.
Yes, excuse me. If you click on the Twitter symbol at the bottom of the screen, you will see this
If you click on the Twitter symbol at the bottom of the screen, you will be able to spread the word about this distribution on Twitter.
Please help us spread the word on Twitter.
Thank you very much.
I would like to start the spreading time here.
I'm going to tweet a notice on Twitter while I'm revueing.
I'm going to tweet an announcement on Twitter during the revue.
So please retweet it.
I'm going to take a picture.
What pose do you want to do?
What do you want to do?
Okay, let's pose as friends.
We're friends.
We're connected.
Thank you very much. Like that.
Okay, well, please retweet me. I'd love to hear from you.
I'll do it. I'll do it. I'll do it today.
I'm okay. Happy autumn.
Too late for fall, too late for New Year's break.
Too late for fall. I'm free to do whatever I want.
I know, I know.
Please be gentle.
Okay, I'd like to go to the corner now.
I'd like to go to the corner for a deep and detailed questionnaire.
Since our last showroom visit was on August 3, it's been almost two months since we last distributed this newsletter, so there's a lot to talk about.
Unfortunately, it is impossible to talk about everything in time, so I would like to take a questionnaire before the talk to decide what I will talk about.
That's what a questionnaire talk is.
Yay!
Shall I announce the theme immediately?
Yes, I will.
What is it?
It's a lot of things.
Here it is.
First of all, let's look at number 1, the middle tone.
Yes. There was one the other day.
And number 2, about the middle period of the album.
Yes. It is now on sale at Juice-on!
Number 3, about Famie.
Let's go back to the past.
And No. 4, about the new member audition camp.
Now, it's Naui, isn't it?Now, it's Naui, isn't it?
And number 5), on the bullet train.
Oh. What's that? It's a word I'm interested in. Number 6, that season has arrived.
What is it? What season is it? No. 8, Tomo-san is here!
This is very interesting. There are seven topics I'm interested in.
We are going to take a survey of the topics that you would like to hear about, and then we will talk about them.
We will take a vote, so please think about which one you would like to hear. Which one do you want to hear? The last three are handwritten.
I wonder what they are. Who or what is it? Let's start the survey!
Let's start! I wonder what they are.
You can tell by the letters, can't you?
But you know, all three of us look rather unrelated today.
They look like each other.
We're all kind of getting closer together.
They look the same.
I think we look more alike than usual.
That's for sure.
It would be scary if we did it with a story that's nobody's business.
What do you think?
Okay, voting is closed.
Five, four, three, two, one, done.
Three, two, one, done.
Too much freedom today.
It was stable.
Yes, so voting is closed.
Yes.
What's the number?
Oh, my gosh, it's Mr. Tou, number 7.
It's overwhelming.
Overwhelming.
I wonder who or what this is.
So, from now on.
I would like to talk about how good my father is. I'm saying, "I like my father. You are the only father I have.
I have been wanting to get a dog since I was a little girl, but it was not easy.
But I finally got a dog in May this year.
He had owned dogs and animals before, so he knew how hard it was, and he always said no. I don't like animals, he said.
He was like, "I don't like animals," and he kept saying no. I was like, "I want to keep an animal," and he kept saying, "I want to keep an animal.
I said I wanted to keep her, but she kept saying no, no, no, no. But when we decided to keep her, she was really reluctant to do so.
But we decided to keep it, but reluctantly,
It was like that.
The father was the first one in the family to get up. Recently, he started to put a camera in the cage to see how the pets are doing, and he sometimes watches them. And he watches it every once in a while. So when I see him getting up in the morning,
And he would say, "I'm getting up in the morning, I'm getting up in the morning, I'm getting up in the morning, I'm getting up in the morning.
Dad. It was recorded,
Ichi ni ichi ni ichi ni" is a signal to go to the bathroom.
It's a signal to go to the bathroom. Ichi ni ichi ni ichi ni. Oh, well done.
Why is that?
It's so cute.
He says he's the cutest guy in the world, even though he's your father.
Oh, Dad.
He was the back-up.
Riku's dad, he looks like... what do you call him?
Duck?
He doesn't seem to talk much.
I have an image of him as a quiet guy,
That's true.
But in front of Uku...
That's great.
You're funny.
That was a bit shocking.
It was so funny I recorded it.
I can show it to my dad when he gets mad at me.
Dad.
I sent it to the family email.
Great.
There was a picture of him hanging out.
It was funny,
Every morning I'd go back and look at the one where he wakes up,
I have a collection.
I bet it's pretty unusual for him to signal to go to the bathroom at 1:00.
Is it?
I don't know, but when I heard "Ichini ni ichi ni ichi ni," I thought, "Is there a certain frenshu?
I thought it might be a certain frenshu.
But I still made a lot of noise about the toilet,
I had been doing that since I was a baby.
I've been doing that since I was a baby,
I've been doing it since I was a baby.
I wonder.
That's strange.
My father's voice responds to mine, too.
I see.
Is there a frequency?
Like the frequency of my father's voice.
It's inside of me.
It says, "This is my father.
Is there a frequency?
He said, "Dad, that's a camera.
It's not his camera.
It's my dad's camera.
It's for recording him.
That's funny.
That's how I felt. That was it.
Now for the next title.
He says you can choose the same one.
I'll take the survey one more time,
Of course, you can pick the same one.
I'll tell the same story.
It can be anything.
You can tell them about your father.
Have you decided? Have you decided? All right, everybody.
We're all set.
Ready?Okay?
Let the voting begin!
Do you care about number 7?
Okay, okay, okay.
That amount of surprise frames.
We've talked about it.
You also care about 5 and 6, don't you?
I'm also very curious about 5 through 4.
I'm really curious about my dad. About my dad.
I wonder.
Whose father is he?
Whose dad is he?
How's it going? How's it going?
I don't know.
Thank you. Thank you, but I'm here for your father.
And we're on deadline in five, four, three, two, one,
That's it!
I wonder.
Whose dad are we talking about?
Oh!
Oh! Oh!
So, this is the number 5 bullet train,
Tenten-ten.
I'm curious. I'm curious about this too.
Who is this?
Yes!
Yes.
He juggled this for me.
I told him gracefully today. On the bullet train.
Yes, this is me.
Quickly.
What is it?
I went to Akita for work recently,
With Riko.
Akita is known for its delicious sake, so I asked her to take me to a sake place,
I wanted to buy some sake on the way back to Akita,
On the way home, I decided to buy some delicious sake,
I bought two bottles of sake.
I said I was looking forward to it, and we got on the Shinkansen to go back to Tokyo.
It was pretty early in the day.
It was pretty early in the game.
I was sitting on the aisle side and Riko was sitting on the window side,
When Riko was about to leave her seat, she hooked the baggage of the person in front of her,
I took all the bags and sake and hung them all there.
Then I told her that I was going to pass by,
I was going to pass by, so I grabbed all the bags at once and decided to put them down because they were so large,
I put the sake on the floor.
I put the sake on the floor and it didn't hit the floor at all.
The sake went down in the bullet train,
I was overcome.
I turned it into an oasis,
Oasis is an expression, isn't it?
I was so happy that I had made it an oasis,
The train is moving pretty fast, so I have to park my seat soon,
I had to stop and take a seat.
I felt that this train was going to turn into sake.
You know, bottles like this.
Yes, and there was one bottle that broke.
The second bottle was safe, so I was happy,
I asked the station staff to call them,
I asked the station staff to come and get it.
The station staff took care of all the broken pieces anyway, and we went home.
I arrived home. Sorry, I just got here suddenly.
Oh, no.
Well, you went home very fast, didn't you?
Yes, I left once.
But thankfully he didn't give you much of a ride.
No, he didn't give me a ride.
And a lot of people were nice to me, so they helped me out.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm so embarrassed.
If it had been a paper bag with apples and oranges...
I would have been a heroine.
Sake!
It was sake, so I said, "I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
And then we went to the root of the house.
The paper bag I was carrying was also wet.
Yes, it was wet.
So the moment I got off the train, I was on the platform of the nearest station, and I had already put the sake in my bag,
I had already put the alcohol in my bag, and all the other small stuff was just rattling around. The paper bag was ripped.
Wow!
And there it was again...
I'm sorry, I'm sorry. I'm sorry. That was embarrassing. Embarrassing. That was amazing. It was kind of a mess. Really bad luck. It was a bad luck today.
I will visit Akita again in November. Oh, I see. That's nice. Akita Japanese. I'm definitely going to buy some.
That's what he said. It's nice. She was a heroine.
I would like to go to the next talk theme.
I'm not sure if I'm going to be able to talk about it,
I don't know, I don't feel confident about what I'm going to say.
I don't know. I might not be chosen.
That's what I hate!
I'm going to say something white!
Don't say white things!
I'm not going to say anything white.
I'm your friend, so I won't be quick.
I won't do it quickly.
Let's start voting!
It doesn't matter if it's the same thing.
Or on the bullet train.
It's about time.
Let's talk about that season.I'm talking about that season.
Indeed. I'm looking forward to what season it is.
I'm glad to be here.
It's the right season, isn't it?
It's embarrassing.
That's right. If this doesn't work out.
I guess so.
What is it?
What do you think?
What do you think is coming?
Did we start?
Are you saying it?
We're starting.
We are.
Yes, we are.
After all, I have to do a lot of this after the white talk.
Five, four, three, two, one.
Voting is closed.
I wonder what we're going to get.
What is it?
It's time for the cheap book.
It's about time to come out
It's about time for the 6 to come out
6, right, Yasumoto-san?
Take that part off.
Good morning.
Take it off, guys. It's hard, it's hard.
Good luck, guys. They're eating you.
You're my friends today, so I'll be tough on you.
Okay, well...
It's that time of year again.
It's here. It's a tough one, this whole thing.
Hearts are going up.
It's that time of year again.
The current season
Hey, there's a lot going on, isn't that what everyone's imagining the most? The tsukimi burger.
Sure, did you eat it? Have you had it? It's delicious.
I think you're expecting a tsukimi burger, but it's not a burger.
It's not? I'm sorry, guys. We're all talking about these funny episodes.
You know what? I...
You love that skin care. I like to study skin care, and I want to talk about one thing today. It's very informative, isn't it? Yes, there is one product that I would like to recommend. What is it? It's a skincare product from Korea called Famu, which you can find at Cosme Kitchen, and they have a serum called Glow Drop. I love it!
I met it last winter, just when I was getting into skincare, and it made me realize how much my skin could change. It is my favorite product. It's called "Glow," so it gives a glow to the skin. It's a moisturizing serum, so you can use it in all seasons, but I avoided it in summer.
I avoided using it in summer. I avoided using it in the summer because I get pimples and such. I sweat a lot, so I avoided using moisturizers that moisturize too much.
Finally, in the fall, when it got colder and drier, I started using it and it was fine. So it's okay now? Look at my skin.
It's so smooth. This is thanks to that serum. That serum has a great balance of moisture, oil, and oil.
The serum has a very good balance of moisture, oil, and oil content. The special formula emulsifies the water and oil and concentrates them into very fine ingredients, so they easily penetrate into the skin.
So, even though it moisturizes the skin, it feels surprisingly smooth after use and does not have that unpleasant sticky feeling.
But when I touch my skin like this, it feels soft, elastic, and supple,
It's as if it's glowing from the bottom of my body, and it makes my skin glow.
That's right! That's why!
That's why I was in the picture, and my camera rules, and even though he's not even wearing any clothes, he glows like a mirror ball.
That's too much light. That was it.
It was amazing.
It was like a glow, wasn't it? It was like a sparkle. I thought it was reflective.
Reflective, right? Yes.
I want to make this go really, really fast. That's great.
It's utopian.
Yeah, that's what I wanted to talk about.
No, but there are a lot of people who are interested. Is anyone here? Hey, guys.
Are you guys seeing this girl?
Are you looking? And the beauty guys. Beauty guys. Men and women have different skin types, and men tend to have more oil on their skin than women. Men's skin tends to be more oily, so they have more pores and various other characteristics.
So, I would like to recommend this serum to those who have already taken care of their skin and have completed the foundation of their skin,
However, you should not use it just because Aya-chan has it. You have to be discerning. Can a man turn into a handsome man?
Yes! Of course. I heard that men with beautiful skin are popular with the ladies.
I see. Skin.
Did you understand? I want you to say the name one last time.
Famire's Glow Drop.
Did you write it down? I did. You wrote it?
Girls? Did you write? Write?
But did you? Beauty boys. Did you write it?
I would like you all to use it. I'll try to use it.
So, this is JAPANET Yasumoto.
Goodbye.
Next
I'm going to score, too. I'm going to go. I hope they choose number 6 a little bit more once more. For a different product again.
That's for sure. I'm concentrating on a different product.
Yes, yes. Wrong. Let's start the voting.
What's the number?
What's the number? What's the number?
Sure thing. You can call me Mr. Tao.
I'd like to hear about all kinds of products.
I wonder. Eviotans.
It says "mirror ball car.
That's nice.
All the fans who came to the show are glowing.
You don't need a point light.
You're glowing too much.
Five, four, three, two, one.
The end!
What is it this time?
What's the number?
What is it?
Too soon!
So, the next topic of the talk will be
My dad!
Hey, aren't you guys interested in 1 through 4?
What's up guys?
I'm just trying to get a handle on this topic that I'm eviscerating.
I was so upset, I broke an earring.
I got upset.Motion.
Oh, no. I just won yesterday.
You're early.
I did it early.
I wonder what it is.
I wonder what's going on.
It's my dad.
My dad.
Dad, are you sure you're not just being recorded on camera? That's what I want to say, but I can't. It's my dad's.
But I'm curious. Rico, when did you start calling him Dad in the first place? I'm curious about that too.
When did you stop? Since you could talk, right?
So, I've been talking about this a lot, haven't I? My mother used to call me Mama.
And, you know, my mom calls me mom when she has kids, and my dad doesn't want to be called dad.
I'm a father.
But I call him Dad.
Why father?
I thought it was normal when I was a kid.
There was a gap, wasn't there? When I first heard it.
What about your brother?
What do you call him?
Your father.
I wonder what he calls him.
Is he my father? He's old enough.
He's my father.
And you're my brother.
He doesn't know "O".
He doesn't know about "O" culture.
What's an "O"? I don't know.
When you were little, you couldn't say "O"?
I don't know, something like that.
Only that kind of thing.
You have to work on your "O".
Babies, or rather, children,
They have a lot of trouble saying words in the beginning.
I think Rico's weakest word was "o".
Papa! Papa! That's what she was saying.
It was a big shock to me. I can't remember when, but I received a call from Rico.
It was from your father. You know that name comes up, right? After I registered it.
It said "Dad.
Is that you? Like... Is he a dad character? I was like, "Dad?
And Riko didn't speak much at that time.
It was the Kozuka era. Probably.
I didn't know anything about Rico.
She tied two knots, and there was this cute little girl,
Dad.
She was a little bit shy, wasn't she?
I was surprised, wasn't I?
That's funny. So, from now on, you can call me Dad.
Yes, I was.
Yes, it was.
You have a lot of dad stories, don't you?
Dad stories.
Okay, then, the next theme.
I think it's a continuing theme.
I think so.
I wonder.
I wonder what it is.
It can be you.
Dad, I'll think about it.
Let's start voting.
I'll have to think about it.
What about Grandma and Grandpa? Grandpa? Grandparents?
I mean... Grandma? Not a culture.
I see. Now that you've done the intro, Grandma and Grandpa are so cute.
Like pants. They're fashionable.
Grandpa and Grandma. That's nice. That's funny.
Well, I'd better go.
Five, four, three, two, one.
That's it!
I wonder.
What's the vote? What's the result?
Oh! Everyone's so serious!
And here we are.
Number one.
The number one!
We're back... backwards and forwards... backwards and forwards... backwards and forwards... our Chūon... our Chūon...
Our newest show. Yes, but it's still interesting, isn't it?
I'm sure everyone's curious.
I thought you weren't interested. I was so surprised.
I was surprised that you weren't interested.
Dad, Dad. I love you guys. Dad, Dad, Dad.
I'm so glad. I'm so glad I went.
The Chūon will be held on September 24th and 25th.
Chichibu Muse Park in Chichibu, Saitama Prefecture, on September 24th and 25th,
How was it? Yes, it was good. This year, I wonder, there are arrangements of songs that are unique to Chūon every year,
This year, there were arrangements of songs that are unique to Chūon.
This year, there are songs that are unique to Chūon, and songs that are not often performed in the usual exciting live concerts.
It is a concert that tends to have a rather unusual setlist, but I feel that the setlist was even more special than in previous years.
They started with "Doshaburi Ligretto," followed by a cover song, and then the Ebitune songs were "Doshaburi Ligretto," "Donten," "Ubu," and "Nikki.
It had been a long time since I had performed these four songs.
I didn't expect them to play these songs.
It was also a shock to me that "Dosunyuri" was the first song from Ebichu.
It was a long time ago when we used to do free live shows.
Free live shows are held outside, so there were many times when it suddenly rained.Free live shows are held outside, so there were many times when it suddenly rained.
In such cases, we would change the setlist on short notice and play the first song in the downpour league.
I see.
It was a time when we were allowed to do whatever we wanted.
There was a time when we did the downpour as the first song at that time,
But we haven't done that since then.
Oh, so that's how it is.
I've seen a lot of downpours in the central arrangement.
It's nice, isn't it? See you again. Moist. It's like a ballad.
And we love it.
We love DONTEN. We love DONTEN.
Oh, my God, I just woke up while singing. I woke up while singing it.
You know. I feel like, you know, DONTEN was released when we were...,
music, so it's an album. 19? Yes, 19.
I don't think there are any fragrant kids or 20 year olds yet.
Maybe around the time I turned 20.
Yeah, I guess.
I was still a child. I hadn't fully grown up yet.
I think my understanding of the world of don stores was still lower than it is now.
It was a very mature and grown-up song.
Now there are 22 of us, and now there are 24 of us.
I think that now that we have 24 members, we have come to know more and more about each other, and have come into contact with more and more different songs.
I'm finally starting to understand the world view of Dongbaek.
I'm starting to understand the world view of the don store. Is Ayaka's 2B the right way to put it?
I felt like I could understand everything, so I was like, "Oh, so that's how it is.
I felt like I could understand everything, so I was like, "Oh, so that's how it is. I was like, "Oh, I see..." That was the best part for me.
It's good, isn't it? I felt like I could understand all the pure and boring movies.
I guess it didn't work out that way.
The main girl liked something different.
We didn't have the same taste.
I won.
I could talk for over an hour about the arguments alone.
You'd seriously win.
Like really watching one movie,
It's as if you're watching a movie with a girl from our generation now as the main character.
The song called "Nikki (Diary)" was written by Kayako Yoshizawa, and it is a rare song that Kayako's song is included in the same live performance,
I was happy to see her song "Diary" in the same live performance, and we got along well with each other. We became good friends.
It's nice, isn't it? Diary songs are good, too.
But you know, we performed the song "Hello!
That's right. It was gorgeous, wasn't it?
It was the first time. That's the first time to perform like that. That's right.
It's the first time. Even if there was no choreography, it was always done on the soundtrack,
It was the first time to perform the song for the first time on a medium-sized soundtrack. That's true.
It was like that. Also, that's right, that's really something, but the percussionist, Mr. Yoshiro Suzuki, gave me that,
You know, he gave us a bell. He gave us a bell. Yes, yes.
What is it? What is that? I wonder how to say "bell of bells. Is it "bells" or "bells"? It's a bunch of bells,
I wonder if they are spare bells for the ones that go off when you shake them. I don't know. I wonder if it's a spare. He had a lot of them and told me I could take this one.
Yes. So, I hung the bell, and when I asked him to walk in the middle, he said to the staff, "When this bell rings, Kobayashi will come.
When this bell rings, it means Kobayashi is coming, so I'll run away. Don't make the bell sound like a bear repellent.
Because, he said, it would be a shang-shang to everyone in the dressing room.
And then the sound came.
Kamachan came running with a smile on her face, and I was already terrified.
It was a horror.
And the tone of the bell was quite low, like a thud.
It was a musical instrument, you know.
It was kind of interesting.
It was like that.
You also wanted to perform a solo.
That's right.
I was able to do a lot of different things.
It was a fun concert.
Okay, last.
I guess it's a talk theme. Can we go on?
We have a little more time, about 10 minutes.
I have about 10 minutes.
Let's go,
Let's start!
Which one do you want?
I can put pressure on everyone, no matter what the flow of the conversation is after I get to the center.
I'm being tested.
We're being tested.
What do you think?
Jesus!
Jesus, that was good!
I'm so glad!
I thought I was going to cry.
What about Jesus?
No, I don't know,
I could finally see it.
Congrats on a great song. I'm happy for you.
I'm glad. I also liked "Light of the Fireflies".
I'm glad.
Are you ready?
Okay, five, four, three, two, one. Voting is closed.
What did we get?
What do you think?
Mom?
What's number four?
Number 4.
New member audition camp.
Quite timely.
The audition itself was finished in August,
It's tomorrow, right?
That's right.
Tomorrow we will announce the new members.
The members will be at a training camp this time,
I joined on the last day,
Unfortunately, Kaho couldn't make it,
I was chasing her at home.
I was chasing after them,
I was able to see how hard everyone was working,I was able to see everyone's efforts in person,
This is your second time, isn't it, Riko?
Yes, yes, I'm going for the second time,
How was it this year? How was it this year, Riko-senpai?
How was it this year?
How was it?
I wonder.
I don't know. I'm waiting for Ashtero.
But what was interesting to see was the three of them.
The new members, who have only been with us for a little over a year, were acting like seniors,
Especially Kunimo-san. It was interesting.
Kunimomo senior, right?
She is trying to be an older sister. But you can't tell how old they are.
There are a lot of kids of the same age.
Mijuashita is 13 years old.
I don't know. It was interesting.
It's true...she's going to be a senior in a year.
But I was like, "What's going on with Fragrant Girl?
When she joined, she was like the first new member in a long time,
So I felt like a senior member, like the other members were my seniors.
I mean, it was the time when we were at the beginning of our career,
In the days before Hinata, new members came in every two months or so,
So the new members who came after us didn't feel like juniors.
They came in with nothing at all, and only changed in those two months.
They didn't really feel like juniors, did they? It's like, "Oh, no, I'm not a junior. If they were the same age, wouldn't they be friends? If they were the same age, they would be friends, right?
That's right, that's right. That's why it's like that.
I guess the three of us have been together for a year, so we don't feel it that much?
I guess so.
I wonder.
Maybe I shouldn't talk about this audition. I'm going to tell them.
Oh no. Oh no.
Let's go next time. Let's go next time.
But there was a karaoke screening by the Japanese singers, wasn't there?
After that, we sang "Cinderella" by Karrie Kinn, which was fun.
It was fun.
It sure was.
I'll do it with my own voice without a microphone.
I might do it with my own voice.
Before that, there was a discussion about the importance of having some kind of individuality in order to get in, so I tried to show my personality.
That was great.
It was amazing. It was amazing. Everyone was so excited.
I guess I'll just have to wait until tomorrow. I hope you enjoy it. I hope everyone who is watching the broadcast now will definitely watch tomorrow's broadcast as well.
That was a close call. That was close. Well then, it's great.
We'll be back soon with the last off-topic. I think this might be the last one.
So let the voting begin!
Okay, I don't mind if we do another skin care one again.
One more Shinkansen story is totally fine.
Shinkansen is fine.
It's closed today.
That's what I'm talking about. Why is Mr. Kobayashi's hair so wet today?
You actually have a lot of stories, don't you, Mr. Kobayashi?
Surprisingly.
About 3 PR items, 2 of them.
About two. Thanks.
I have 7,000 shocking, shocking stories that end in a second, and a wet story.
A wet story.
If they pick number 5, that's the story?
Five, four, three, two, one,
No, no, no, no, no.
You're starting again. That's what I'm talking about.
Yes. I wonder which one it was.
That's enough. That's enough.
Yes, this is now Sosanger, number 7.
You guys are as good as I expected.
This is Main Street.
My dad. Do it. Do you have it? Everyone who's watching this distribution, you guys do it. I'll do it.
I see. Let's all listen to Riko's story about her dad's camera with fresh faces. I'm sure we will.
And the comments, too. Let's go back to the basics. Understand? Listen with hands you don't know.
Who's my dad again?
I don't know. It's me.
Riko.
Riko-chan.
May I?
I got a puppy in May this year.
Was I right?
I've had a puppy since May, and I've been in elementary school since then.
I had been going to pet stores to get a puppy, but they kept saying no. I knew it would be hard to take care of her, and it would be too much work.
I knew it would be hard to take care of him, and it would be hard to take care of him.
My father was the only one in my family who had a lot of animals when I was young,
He was the only one in the family who had a lot of animals when he was a child, so he knew how hard it was to keep animals.
He knew that, and he was the first one to say no. He said, "No, you can't. He said, "No. I don't like animals.
I don't like animals. He was in denial. So it was a no-go. But in May of this year, we decided to buy it, and at that time, there was a sign.
I don't know what it was, but it was like, "You have to look at the meds properly. It was like that. Recently, however, we started putting a head camera near the cage, so we had a camera that we could watch 24 hours a day, 7 days a week.
The father is the first one in the family to get up. From inside the office.
When he first wakes up, he cleans the dog's toilet and so on,
And when he was watching the pet camera, he said, "Oh!
Oh!
Wait a minute.
What?
It's predictable.
You're gonna put me through to your pet's camera, aren't you?
Wait a minute.
What?
Oh, my God! It's coming!
What? What? What? I'm scared, I'm scared! I've never heard my story before. That season? That season?
Yes, that season. That's it, isn't it? Your father petting a cudgel, saying, "One, two, one, two, ah, well done," right?
I'm looking at my family's shared pet camera. It's leaking. It's leaking into the Nakayama family. Be careful.
It's bad, isn't it? Only four people in the family can see it. Is that true? Is that true?
It's true.
Oh, no!Oh no!
It was a scary story.
That's all,
This is Survey Talk.
Survey talk.
It was a scary story.
It's scary to be made to tell the same story twice, isn't it?
It's scary, isn't it?
It's always scary, isn't it?
I told it three times.
That means it's scary. This is the 49th edition of Bichu's funny and fluffy showroom, and in no time at all, it will be ending at the same time as the last edition.
Thank you very much. That was great. That was great. We talked about a lot of things. We talked about all kinds of things.
Most of it was about my dad. I'd like to hear more, wouldn't you?
Yes, of course. I want to know how many viewers Riko's father has.
I really want to meet him now. I want to meet Riko's father.
I want to meet him. I want to go see him. I want to go there. I heard it live.
Okay, so I'm going to make an announcement here.
Let's see.... Yes, in December.
On December 16th, there will be a graduation live of Hinata Kashiwagi. And the next day, December 17th, we will have our first live as a new group.
The venue is Makuhari Messe Event Hall, so please check it out.
Please check it out. As I mentioned earlier, tomorrow, October 1, we will announce our new members.
We will announce the new members tomorrow, October 1. The announcement will be made live at 8:00 p.m.
I'm very excited to see what kind of members have been chosen.
So, Dad, please. I'm not Dad.
I'm not your father.
On Monday, October 24th, Riko Nakayama's birthday solo live will be held at KTZEP Yokohama.
What are you laughing at?
Sorry, I just got called "Dad" by a new member.
I'm in the house!
I'm not going to say it again.
I thought maybe it was my dad.
I don't know. It could be him.
It could be my dad.
Suddenly he's very nimble.
I don't know.
I'll take it back. I'm not sure if I'm going to be able to make it.
I'll be at KTZP Yokohama at 7pm. General tickets go on sale tomorrow at 10:00.
So will you be climbing the mountain at this center? I will definitely be there!
I'm not going to perform.
Yes, he will. I think he will probably come.
He will be here.
He said 1,2,1,2.
I recognized her from Miko, she said 1,2,1,2.
I'm scared. I'm scared.
Yuko, you made it. That's great.
You're too scary.
It's funny.
Please, everyone.
I'm counting on you all.
I think I'll check out the final ranking.
I'll check the final ranking.
Miko, are you going to announce it?
That's great.
Thank you, Mr. Lobo.
No. 4, 0607. Thank you very much.
3rd place, Mr. Tuna, thank you very much.
2nd place, Penrabunbun, thank you very much!
And 1st place, Ko-chan Movie. Thank you.
Thank you very much.
That was fun.
It all went by so fast, didn't it?
It's really kind of a mess today... what is it?
It's like I'm talking to a café. Like if the three of us went to a cafe or something like this.
I think that's why I was able to deliver the message.
Is that okay? Is there anything else? Is there anything you want to say?
Do you have any last skincare recommendations? I'm curious!
Is that okay? I just have one more recommendation for you.
Thank you very much!
I would like to recommend a face pack from an anti-aging line by a company called Minon.
I highly recommend this pack.
It is a thick, thick, dense liquid that is perfect for this season, and you put it on your face,
It is an anti-aging care product, so it can improve the elasticity and firmness of the skin,
As is typical with skin care packs, the last of the liquid remains in the bag. It's in the bag.
It's a waste, so you want to use it all.
There is a way to use it by dripping it on the skin like this, isn't there?
Yes, there is.
But if you drip it on your skin, it all drips down your neck.
That's true.
But this is a very dense liquid, so it doesn't drip,
It can be absorbed into the skin until the very end.
Isn't this a very cost-effective product?
You can use up the entire liquid. I hope everyone will buy this face pack as well.
Are you a Minon rep or a vendor? Are you a vendor?
I want to be a vendor someday. I want to.
Then, everyone who is looking for a face pack, please go buy one. Just go in.
Just in. They're cheap, folks. It's easy to buy.
And that brings us to the end of the 49th edition of Bichu's Delightful and Fluffy Showroom.
An important announcement. The next broadcast will be on Sunday, October 23rd at 19:00.
Please make a note of it.
This broadcast will also include a review meeting that will take place afterwards, so be sure to check it out.
We will resume in a few minutes, so please stay tuned.
If you have anything you would like to tell us at the meeting, please feel free to leave a comment.
Please do so.
Please, please, please, please.
Please do.
That's all for now, we are fresh and dense.
Bye bye!
Please subscribe to our channel.Please subscribe to our channel.
I wonder if Nanchan will be around much longer?
I wonder if she'll be around much longer?
We still look a bit like him.
Rampage.
The day before last, he ate my right leg.
Riko's right leg?
Was it good?
That's cute.
But getting your leg bitten by a dog is so soothing.
It doesn't hurt, does it?
It hurts.
It hurts. Okay, then.
Float a little.
That's so cool.
You're so cute.
Good night, sweetie.
Good night, sweetheart.
It's comforting, really.
I'm gonna need my dad, but...
Hmm?
Yeah, 1212.
I'm gonna need my dad's frequency.
Or I'm gonna need Riko's dad.
Yeah, that's a big deal.
Oh, my God.
Yeah, it's going to be hard.
It's gonna be tough.
It's gonna be hard.
Oh, my God.
Let's get him here.
Oh, my God. My dad's in trouble.
Oh, my God, Dad. Oh, my God.
Thank you for your hard work.
Thank you very much.
You did a lot of talking today.
I did.
But...
We talked a lot.
It was very noisy backstage, wasn't it?
Yes, it was.
That's what I thought.
We talked all the time.
But you know what?
He was taking Instagram stories.
That's right, that's right.
You gotta see this.
See what?
Look at the story.
It wasn't any different when we were doing it backstage.
Yes, it did.
Just the same.
We had a gorgeous set up, the two of us.
As it was.
I had to get out of the way.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
We're here because we're friends.
Because we're friends.
We're friends.
I was just thinking...
I don't know...
You know, the three of us...
Like, "Hey, we're friends today, right?
After we were on LINE...
You know...
I'm the educator.
So...
That's right.
Now...
Looking at the three of you...
Two of them are...
You're the educators.
You're with the three of them.
I wonder if it'll turn out that way later on.
I don't know.
But there's a gap of about eight years.
Even Cocona is 5 years old.
So there's a gap.
That's not why.
It's just that it's so strange.
But you said it.
I see.
Four years.
With the fragrant girl.
How long have I been out?
About four years.
I'm free.
Age.
I don't know.
Maybe I'm right.
I think he's just surprisingly picky.
Even though he's two years older than me.
That's true.
He's just a friend.
I don't even know his parents.I don't even have parents at all.
I mean, it's not like I'm the neighbor's sister or anything.
If anything, I'm being advised by both of them.
I know.
It's not weird.
I don't like it.
It's not strange that we're acting like we're the seniors.
You're right.
It's like, what are you gonna do?
Next time you see me, act like a senior.
I can't.
Tomorrow?
Act like it's tomorrow.
At this point, I don't know.
Go get me some coffee.
It's time to reflect.
It's really summer.
Backstage tension.
You can talk backstage.
That's what we're sending out to the community.
So this is reflection.
That's right.
That's today's reflection.
Well, close it then.
I don't have any reflections.
Okay, then.
I don't know when I'll be around again.
About a year, right?
Maybe a year.
Have a good New Year's for once.
Thank you very much.
Bye-bye.
Huffing and puffing
Thank you for watching